{"response_code":0,
        "results":[
					{ 
						"category":"Nurture",
						"type":"multiple",
						"difficulty":"hard",
						"question":" Equity/equality ",
						"correct_answer":"Equity",
						"incorrect_answers":["Equality"]
						
					},
					{
						"category":"Nurture",
						"type":"multiple",
						"difficulty":"medium",
						"question":" Order/Arrangement ",
						"correct_answer":"Order",
						"incorrect_answers":["Arrangement"]
					},
		
						{
						"category":"Nurture",
						"type":"multiple",
						"difficulty":"medium",
						"question":"Truth/fact",
						"correct_answer":"Truth",
						"incorrect_answers":["Fact"]
					},
		
						{
						"category":"Nurture",
						"type":"multiple",
						"difficulty":"medium",
						"question":"Intelligence/brilliance",
						"correct_answer":"Intelligence",
						"incorrect_answers":["Brilliance"]
					},
	                                 {
						"category":"Nurture",
						"type":"multiple",
						"difficulty":"medium",
						"question":" Understanding/knowledge ",
						"correct_answer":"Understanding",
						"incorrect_answers":["Knowledge"]
					},
		                        {
						"category":"Nurture",
						"type":"multiple",
						"difficulty":"medium",
						"question":" Wealth/money ",
						"correct_answer":"Wealth",
						"incorrect_answers":["Money"]
					},
		{
						"category":"Nurture",
						"type":"multiple",
						"difficulty":"medium",
						"question":"Love/fear",
						"correct_answer":"Love",
						"incorrect_answers":["Fear"]
					},
		
		                        {
						"category":"Nurture",
						"type":"multiple",
						"difficulty":"medium",
						"question":" Home/house/family ",
						"correct_answer":"Family",
						"incorrect_answers":["Home","House"]
					},
		
		                        {
						"category":"Nurture",
						"type":"multiple",
						"difficulty":"medium",
						"question":"Trust/believe/confidence  ",
						"correct_answer":"Trust",
						"incorrect_answers":["Believe","Confidence"]
					},
		
		                        {
						"category":"Nurture",
						"type":"multiple",
						"difficulty":"medium",
						"question":" Peace/Rest/Quiet ",
						"correct_answer":"Peace",
						"incorrect_answers":["Rest","Quiet"]
					},
		
			{
						"category":"Nurture",
						"type":"multiple",
						"difficulty":"medium",
						"question":"Intimate/close/familiar",
						"correct_answer":"Intimate",
						"incorrect_answers":["Close","Familiar"]
					},	
		
			{
						"category":"Nurture",
						"type":"multiple",
						"difficulty":"medium",
						"question":"Far/Distant",
						"correct_answer":"Distant",
						"incorrect_answers":["Far"]
					},
		{
						"category":"Nurture",
						"type":"multiple",
						"difficulty":"medium",
						"question":"Half full/half empty ",
						"correct_answer":"Half Full",
						"incorrect_answers":["Half empty"]
					},		

		{
						"category":"Nurture",
						"type":"multiple",
						"difficulty":"medium",
						"question":"Punishment/Correction/Chastisement ",
						"correct_answer":"Chastisement",
						"incorrect_answers":["Punishment", "Correction"]
				},		
		

		{
						"category":"Nurture",
						"type":"multiple",
						"difficulty":"medium",
						"question":"Hard/Difficult",
						"correct_answer":"Difficult",
						"incorrect_answers":["Hard"]
				},		


		
				]
}
1. Fairness with example. E.g who deserves the bed, A pregnant woman or a crippled man.

2. Which is more appropriate

3. Which is practical

4. Similar or better?

5. Which is more expensive?

6. Similar or better?

7. Strongest Emotional trigger

8. Describe where you grew

9. Range between 1-10

10. Which is easier to achieve? 

11. Foe or friend

12. Hope for prospects

13. Sincere to a fault

14. Judge of character. (optimist or pessimist)

15. Stress pattern/pain
